

I'm a UI designer with a background in philology, finance, photography and graphic design. Due to my diverse professional experience I am able to adapt to different environments while adhering to professional integrity. Besides arts and creating, I love developing my skills, learning new tools and improving my design skillset, while making aesthetically pleasing and useful products and interfaces.

#### PERSONAL DATA

Ossastrasse 41, 12045, Berlin

+49 1797296729

kata.serfozo@gmail.com

Be www.behance.net/kataserfozo

## PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Photoshop
Lightroom
Illustrator
InDesign
Balsamique
Sketch
InVision
Principle
html, css

## LANGUAGE SKILLS

Hungarian
English
Swedish
German

### **EXTRACURRICULAR**

- 6 months in New Zealand on a working holiday scheme
- 3 months experience as a barista in London
- Volunteering for 3 months in Portugal in a surf camp
- Working as a freelance photographer and weddings
- Experience in Studio Photography

# **COURSES AND TRAININGS**

- Interaction Design specialization (Coursera)
- Certificates in Graphic Design,
   Photoshop, Illustrator, Lightroom and InDesign (Shawacademy, Udemy)

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

09/2018- present UI Design course CareerFoundry

- UI design for music, messaging, note-taking applications
- UX and UI design for cooking application for mobile and responsive design
- UI design for delivery application for iOS and Android Native app
- UI design for money saving responsive website

10/2017 – 3/2018 Graphic and Web Design intern
 MediaSales, Budapest, Hungary

- · Creating banners, website and mobile interface design
- Creating images and ads for social media and presentations
- Designing products for print

04/2014 – 12/2016 Reporting Specialist
 British Telecom, Budapest, Hungary

- Designing and maitaining database of employees in Business Objects application
- Creating and running reports for management on employe utilisation rates on projects and project expenditures for forecasting pruposes
- Testing corporate data warehouse of the time, labour and project management tool
- Performing data cleanse and data analysis activities
- Controlling and updating labour rate card data

11/2013 - 03/2014 Finance Professional
British Telecom, Budapest, Hungary

- Providing 1st Line Support for a Project and People Management System
- Performing system administration activities
- Explaining and looking for solutions for the users of the Management System

### **EDUCATION**

01/2010 - 06/2010 Rønde Højskole , Rønde, Denmark
 Arts, Project Management

© 09/2009 - 12/2013 Eötvös Loránd University, Budapest, Hungary BA, English and Scandinavian Studies